Voices of Civil Rights Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series I: Manuscripts, 2003-2006
  - Subseries II: Submissions, 2003-2004, 1612 folders
    - Johnson, Rosa Merriweather (Box-folder 12/63)
    - Johnson, Rosemary (Box-folder 12/64)
    - Johnson, Veronica (Box-folder 12/65)
    - Johnson, Warren I. (Box-folder 12/66)
    - Johnson, Willette P. (Box-folder 12/67)
    - Johnson, William H. (Box-folder 12/68)
    - Jonas, Jason W. (Box-folder 12/69)
    - Jones, Alice N. (Box-folder 12/70)
    - Jones, Gladys Lee (Box-folder 12/71)
    - Jones, Henry L., Jr. (Box-folder 12/72)
    - Jones, John L. (Box-folder 12/73)
    - Jones, Linda (Box-folder 12/74)
    - Jones, Luvenia (Box-folder 12/75)
    - Jones, Lyle (Box-folder 12/76)
    - Jones, Margie (Box-folder 12/77)
    - Jones, Phyllis R. (Box-folder 12/78)
    - Jones, Sandra (Box-folder 12/79)
    - Jones, Willie C. (Box-folder 12/80)
    - Jones, Willie (Bill) L. (Box-folder 12/81)
    - Jordan, Carolyne Lamar (Box-folder 12/82)
    - Jordan, Gail (Box-folder 12/83)
    - Jordan, John E. (Box-folder 12/84)
    - Jordan, L. J. (Box-folder 12/85)
      Contains poem.
    - Jordan, Lawrence M. (Box-folder 12/86)
    - Jordan, Robert A. (Box-folder 12/87)
    - Jorgensen, Russell F. and Mary L. (Box-folder 12/88)
    - Joslyn, Wallace Danforth (Box-folder 12/89)
    - Kahn, Truman (Box-folder 13/1)
    - Kalina, Victor (Box-folder 13/2)
    - Kaluenja, Joan Wiggins (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Kates, James (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Kaufman, Dorothy A. (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Keaner, Jesse (Box-folder 13/6)
    - Keating, John (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Kechele, Keys (Box-folder 13/8)
    - Keeton, Lee Elvin, Sr. (Box-folder 13/9)
    - Kehrein, Glen (Box-folder 13/10)
    - Keith, Terry (Box-folder 13/11)
    - Kelchner, Bruce (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Kelly, Jane (Box-folder 13/13)
    - Kelso, Shirley Johnson (Box-folder 13/14)
    - Kennedy, Joseph, Sr. (Box-folder 13/15)
    - Kessler, Keith (Box-folder 13/16)
    - Ketchum, David (Box-folder 13/17)
    - Khan, M. J. (Box-folder 13/18)
    - Khedouri, Amy (Box-folder 13/19)
    - Khiev, Chantal (Box-folder 13/20)
    - Kiah, Maggie (Box-folder 13/21)
    - Kiefer, Anne Zoller Herzog (Box-folder 13/22)
    - Kiener, Carol (Box-folder 13/23)
    - Kilgore, Alberta G. (Box-folder 13/24)
    - Killingsworth, Patricia (Box-folder 13/25)
    - Kim, Jin (Box-folder 13/26)
    - Kincade, Barbara (Box-folder 13/27)
    - Kinchlow, David M. (Box-folder 13/28)
    - King, Bernie (Box-folder 13/29)
    - King, Cynthia Hatch (Box-folder 13/30)
    - King, Dawn (Box-folder 13/31)
    - King, Georgia A. (Box-folder 13/32)
      Includes photographs, news clippings, and short biographies.
    - King, Gerry (Box-folder 13/33)
    - King, John E. (Box-folder 13/34)
    - King, Steven C. (Box-folder 13/35)
    - King-Miller, C. Tasmiya (Box-folder 13/36)
    - Kingsley, Ginny (Box-folder 13/37)
    - Kircher, Joyce Megginson (Box-folder 13/38)
    - Kirk, Carol (Box-folder 13/39)
    - Kitayama, Kay (Box-folder 13/40)
    - Kitchens, Willie B. (Box-folder 13/41)
    - Klau, Judith (Box-folder 13/42)
    - Klein, Arthur (Box-folder 13/43)
    - Klein, Ruth S. (Box-folder 13/44)
    - Klein, Walter J. (Box-folder 13/45)
    - Kleiss, Lee Maria (Box-folder 13/46)
    - Klessig, Lowell (Box-folder 13/47)
    - Klevansky, Richard (Box-folder 13/48)
    - Kline, Elizabeth (Box-folder 13/49)
    - Knight, Jenn (Box-folder 13/50)
    - Knight, Lessie B. (Box-folder 13/51)
    - Knott, Garland (Box-folder 13/52)
    - Knudsen, Gerald (Box-folder 13/53)
    - Koch, Audrey Straus (Box-folder 13/54)
    - Koglin, Oznathylee (Box-folder 13/55)
    - Konnick, David E. (Box-folder 13/56)
    - Konrad, William Wesley (Box-folder 13/57)
    - Koptish, Georgene (Box-folder 13/58)
    - Korpela, Janet Winn (Box-folder 13/59)
    - Kreiner, Ruth A. (Box-folder 13/60)
    - Kripke, Derril K. (Box-folder 13/61)
    - Krol, Debra (Box-folder 13/62)
    - Kroner, Ada (Box-folder 13/63)
    - Kumar, Tobi J. (Box-folder 13/64)
    - Kunz, Helen L. (Box-folder 13/65)
    - LaChapelle, Gloria (Box-folder 13/66)
    - Lacorvara, Joyce (Box-folder 13/67)
    - LaMarche, G. Venora (Box-folder 13/68)
    - Lamasney, Richard (Box-folder 13/69)
    - Lamb, Dean H. (Box-folder 13/70)
    - Lambert, Catherine A. (Box-folder 13/71)
    - Lamborghini, Carolyn (Box-folder 13/72)
    - Landreville, Nancy M. (Box-folder 13/73)
    - Landsman, Julie (Box-folder 13/74)
    - Lang, Ruth (Box-folder 13/75)
    - Langbert, Ruth (Box-folder 13/76)
    - Langdon, Kathy (Box-folder 13/77)
    - Lanier, Paul (Box-folder 13/78)
    - Lansey, Sheryl (Box-folder 13/79)
    - Lansey, Yvonne F. (Box-folder 13/80)
    - LaPorte, Jewel Lee Miller (Box-folder 13/81)
    - Larrabee, William (Box-folder 13/82)
    - Larsha, William M. (Box-folder 13/83)
      Contains pamphlet copies.
    - Latham, Joyce (Box-folder 14/1)
    - Latting, Jean Kantambu (Box-folder 14/2)
    - Lauria, Amedeo (Box-folder 14/3)
    - Lawrence, Frankie (Box-folder 14/4)
    - Lawrence, Richard (Box-folder 14/5)
    - Lawson, Gloria (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Lawson, Joseph Henry (Box-folder 14/7)
    - Lax, Debra (Box-folder 14/8)
    - Layng, Anthony (Box-folder 14/9)
    - Le Vie, Jane (Box-folder 14/10)
    - Leach, Oliver (Box-folder 14/11)
      Includes a letter, two photographs, an article, military papers, and Supreme Court Docket information.
    - Laclercq, Elaine (Box-folder 14/12)
    - Lee, Andre L. (Box-folder 14/13)
    - Lee, Charles (Box-folder 14/14)
    - Lee, Fann Shirley (Box-folder 14/15)
    - Lee, J. Kenneth (Box-folder 14/16)
    - Lee, James E. (Box-folder 14/17)
    - Lee, Margie (Box-folder 14/18)
    - Lefor, Arnold (Box-folder 14/19)
      Includes a letter, flyers, newspaper photograph, and release forms.
    - Leiby, Zera C. (Box-folder 14/20)
    - Leigh, Mildred (Box-folder 14/21)
      Includes magazine photograph.
    - Lemes, Beverlee (Box-folder 14/22)
    - Lenhoff, Howard (Box-folder 14/23)
    - Leondar, Arnol (Box-folder 14/24)
    - Lepionka, Mary Ellen (Box-folder 14/25)
    - Lester, Joan Steinau (Box-folder 14/26)
    - Lester, Sylvia C. (Box-folder 14/27)
    - Leventhal, William E. (Box-folder 14/28)
    - Levin, Arthur J. (Box-folder 14/29)
    - Lewis, Allan (Box-folder 14/30)
    - Lewis, B. J. (Box-folder 14/31)
    - Lewis, Bernadette C. (Box-folder 14/32)
    - Lewis, Richard J. (Box-folder 14/33)
    - Lewis-Epps, Rennie B. (Box-folder 14/34)
      Includes photographs and news clippings.
    - Libby, Paula Quandt (Box-folder 14/35)
    - Lincoln, Gary (Box-folder 14/36)
    - Lindsay, C. Cary (Box-folder 14/37)
    - Lisante, Joan E. (Box-folder 14/38)
    - Litchfield, James E. (Box-folder 14/39)
    - Little, Mattie T. (Box-folder 14/40)
      Includes book excerpt.
    - Livingston, Sandy (Box-folder 14/41)
    - Livingston, William (Box-folder 14/42)
    - Lnenicka, Wade S. (Box-folder 14/43)
    - Lock, Eugene R. (Box-folder 14/44)
    - Lock, Eva (Box-folder 14/45)
    - Lockhart, Elise A. (Box-folder 14/46)
    - Lockwood, Gary (Box-folder 14/47)
    - Logan, Hazel N. (Box-folder 14/48)
    - Logan, Richard L. (Box-folder 14/49)
      Includes booklet.
    - Lohrke, Barbara (Box-folder 14/50)
    - Long, Hester (Box-folder 14/51)
    - Long, Mary (Box-folder 14/52)
    - Lopez, Hugo R. (Box-folder 14/53)
      Includes author biographical information.
    - Lout, James M. (Box-folder 14/54)
    - Loutzenhiser, Richard M. (Box-folder 14/55)
    - Lovekin, Joan A. (Box-folder 14/56)
    - Lovelace, Karen (Box-folder 14/57)
    - Lowe, Sandra (Box-folder 14/58)
    - Lu, Scylla (Box-folder 14/59)
    - Luening, Margery P. (Box-folder 14/60)
    - Lum, Lydia (Box-folder 14/61)
    - Lutz, James (Box-folder 14/62)
    - Lykes, Mary Hardy (Box-folder 14/63)
    - Lynch, Constance A. (Box-folder 14/64)
    - Lynch, Louise (Box-folder 14/65)
    - Lyte, Phyllis (Box-folder 14/66)
    - Mackey, Mae Frances Bray (Box-folder 14/67)
    - Madeley, Suzann (Box-folder 14/68)
    - Magee, Raymond J. (Box-folder 14/69)
      Includes a letter and brochure.
    - Magilton, Natalie S. (Box-folder 14/70)
    - Mainiero, Elizabeth (Box-folder 14/71)
    - Malone, James Hiram (Box-folder 14/72)
    - Malone, Sheila (Box-folder 14/73)
    - Mandel, Charlotte (Box-folder 14/74)
    - Manney, Kathryn (Box-folder 14/75)
    - Manousos, Donald B. (Box-folder 15/1)
    - Manuel, Bettie (Box-folder 15/2)
    - Marez, Maria Crestena (Box-folder 15/3)
    - Marks, Michael (Box-folder 15/4)
      Includes poster and programs for high school play "Freedom Summer."
    - Marney, Elaine B. (Box-folder 15/5)
    - Maro, Marsha Campbell (Box-folder 15/6)
    - Maron, Norma (Box-folder 15/7)
    - Marsano, Robert M. (Box-folder 15/8)
    - Marsh, Frederick (Box-folder 15/9)
    - Marshall-Varela, Veronica (Box-folder 15/10)
    - Martilotto, Valentino (Box-folder 15/11)
    - Martin, Aaron E. (Box-folder 15/12)
    - Martin, B. Herbert (Box-folder 15/13)
    - Martin, Joyce (Box-folder 15/14)
    - Mashariki, Job (Box-folder 15/15)
    - Mason, Joan (Box-folder 15/16)
    - Massey, Minnie Lee T. (Box-folder 15/17)
    - Matathias, Asher J. (Box-folder 15/18)
    - Mau'Dib, Sofessor (Don Murray) (Box-folder 15/19)
    - Mauer, George (Box-folder 15/20)
    - Maxwell, Thomas J. (Box-folder 15/21)
    - Mayfield, Thomas (Box-folder 15/22)
    - Mays, Ruth (Box-folder 15/23)
    - Mazzagatti, Donald (Box-folder 15/24)
    - McAllister, Greg (Box-folder 15/25)
    - McCamant, Mary Jane (Box-folder 15/26)
    - McCarren, Barbara J. (Box-folder 15/27)
    - McCarty, Catherine C. (Box-folder 15/28)
    - McCauley, Marianne DiPalermo (Box-folder 15/29)
    - McClellan, Robert (Box-folder 15/30)
    - McCoy, Ann A. (Box-folder 15/31)
    - McCoy, John D. (Box-folder 15/32)
    - McCray, Ernie (Box-folder 15/33)
    - McCudden, Shirley (Box-folder 15/34)
    - McCullough, Lloyd D. (Box-folder 15/35)
    - McFadden, James S. (Box-folder 15/36)
      Includes news clipping and biography.
    - McFadden, Ruby (Box-folder 15/37)
    - McGaffin, Donald E. (Box-folder 15/38)
    - McGhee, Charles (Box-folder 15/39)
    - McGhee-Anderson, Kathleen (Box-folder 15/40)
      Includes news articles and photographs.
    - McGown, David J. (Box-folder 15/41)
    - McGruder, Julious (Box-folder 15/42)
    - McIntyre, Catherine (Box-folder 15/43)
    - McLaughlin, Edward (Box-folder 15/44)
    - McLaughlin, Larry (Box-folder 15/45)
    - McLearen, Bob (Box-folder 15/46)
    - McLeod, Hyacinth (Box-folder 15/47)
    - McLeod, Laura Kay (Box-folder 15/48)
    - McMahan, Elizabeth Anne (Box-folder 15/49)
    - McMahon, Gerald F. (Box-folder 15/50)
    - McMullin, William (Box-folder 15/51)
    - McMurray, Edward B. (Box-folder 15/52)
    - McNeely, Jessie Mae (Box-folder 15/53)
    - McWilliams, Roscoe (Box-folder 15/54)
    - Meade, Betty (Box-folder 15/55)
    - Megyeri, Kathy (Box-folder 15/56)
    - Meier, Ruth C. (Box-folder 15/57)
    - Meinhardt, Lynn (Box-folder 15/58)
    - Meredith, Verle Lucille (Box-folder 15/59)
    - Merritt, Betty L. (Box-folder 15/60)
    - Merritt, Karen Whitney (Box-folder 15/61)
    - Mersky, Roy M. (Box-folder 15/62)
    - Metersky, Mort (Box-folder 15/63)
    - Meuler, Andrew W. (Box-folder 15/64)
      2 original .doc files available.
      Includes transcripts of interviews conducted by students at Rufus King High School in Milwaukee, Wisconsin.
    - Michael, Randy S. (Box-folder 15/65)
    - Millenson, Roy H. (Box-folder 15/66)
    - Miller, Elizabeth W. (Box-folder 15/67)
    - Miller, Jacqueline B. (Box-folder 15/68)
    - Mills, Barbara (Box-folder 15/69)
    - Mills, Igalious (Box-folder 15/70)
      Includes biography, news clippings and correspondence.
    - Mills, Roger (Box-folder 15/71)
    - Mims, Rosa Lee (Box-folder 15/72)
    - Minor, Margaret (Box-folder 15/73)
    - Mitchell, Johnnie Wilcher (Box-folder 15/74)
    - Mitchell-Rowlett, Lois P. (Box-folder 15/75)
    - Mohr, Jeani Hancock (Box-folder 15/76)
    - Molloy, Edward T. (Box-folder 15/77)
    - Monaco, Daniel J. (Box-folder 15/78)
    - Moore, Lenore K. (Box-folder 16/1)
    - Moore, Velma (Box-folder 16/2)
    - Morgan, Frank (Box-folder 16/3)
    - Morgan, Mike (Box-folder 16/4)
    - Morganstern, Marian (Box-folder 16/5)
    - Morris, Alma R. (Box-folder 16/6)
    - Morris, Harryette (Box-folder 16/7)
    - Morrison, David R. (Box-folder 16/8)
    - Morrison, Ralph J. (Box-folder 16/9)
    - Morton, Dianne N. (Box-folder 16/10)
    - Moseley, Larry D. (Box-folder 16/11)
    - Moseley, Rita (Box-folder 16/12)
    - Mosellie, Weda M. (Box-folder 16/13)
    - Mosley, Johnnie (Box-folder 16/14)
    - Moss, Robert (Box-folder 16/15)
    - Mueller, James L. (Box-folder 16/16)
    - Muhammad, Thomas (Box-folder 16/17)
    - Mullen, Esther G. (Box-folder 16/18)
    - Mullins, Pamela (Box-folder 16/19)
    - Munson, Mary (Box-folder 16/20)
    - Munson, Patricia (Box-folder 16/21)
    - Murdock, Sandra P. (Box-folder 16/22)
    - Murphy, Delores (Box-folder 16/23)
    - Murray, Paul T. (Box-folder 16/24)
    - Mushroom, Merril (Box-folder 16/25)
    - Myers, David (Box-folder 16/26)
    - Nail-Taylor, Emma (Box-folder 16/27)
    - Nash, Curtis E. (Box-folder 16/28)
    - Neagu, George V. (Box-folder 16/29)
    - Nelson, Regina (Box-folder 16/30)
    - Nelson, Ruth E. (Box-folder 16/31)
    - Nesbitt, Veronica Brady (Box-folder 16/32)
    - Newby, Nanette (Box-folder 16/33)
    - Newsum, Floyd E., Sr. (Box-folder 16/34)
      Includes postcard and book excerpt.
    - Nichols, Robert L. (Box-folder 16/35)
    - Niece, Gerald L. (Box-folder 16/36)
    - Niemann, Robert A. (Box-folder 16/37)
    - Norcross, Steve (Box-folder 16/38)
    - Nord, Myrtle S. (Box-folder 16/39)
    - Nottingham, Angela B. (Box-folder 16/40)
    - Nunnally, Melvin C. (Box-folder 16/41)
    - Nyamu, Beneva D. (Box-folder 16/42)
      Includes articles.
    - Nyangoni, Betty (Box-folder 16/43)
    - O'Brien, Helen (Box-folder 16/44)
    - O'Brien, John T. (Box-folder 16/45)
    - O'Keefe, Lois (Box-folder 16/46)
    - O'Leary, Emerald (Box-folder 16/47)
    - Oliver, Kitty (Box-folder 16/48)
    - Oliver, Marc R. (Box-folder 16/49)
    - Oliver, Nancy J. (Box-folder 16/50)
    - Olson, Norman (Box-folder 16/51)
    - Ono, Noboru (Box-folder 16/52)
    - O'Rouke, Loraine (Box-folder 16/53)
    - Orucutt, Albert W. (Box-folder 16/54)
    - Osgood, Mary Jo (Box-folder 16/55)
    - Oskamp, Barbara H. (Box-folder 16/56)
    - Owens, Essie D. (Box-folder 16/57)
    - Owens, Hugo A., Sr. (Box-folder 16/58)
      Includes articles and photocopies of photographs.
    - Pacheco, Mary (Box-folder 16/59)
    - Packwood, Wayne E. (Box-folder 16/60)
    - Paden, Renee L. (Box-folder 16/61)
    - Paris, Charlotte Quick (Box-folder 16/62)
    - Parker, Frances Shani (Box-folder 16/63)
    - Parker, Michael D. (Box-folder 16/64)
    - Parks, Clarissa (Box-folder 16/65)
    - Parks, George B. (Box-folder 16/66)
    - Parks, Lynette (Box-folder 16/67)
    - Parrish, Wilma F. (Box-folder 16/68)
    - Parsley, Charles J. (Box-folder 16/69)
    - Partridge, Frederick W., Jr. (Box-folder 16/70)
    - Patterson, Bettie (Box-folder 16/71)
    - Patterson, Carol Anne (Box-folder 16/72)
    - Patterson, Georgia (Box-folder 16/73)
    - Patterson, Lemuel Allen (Box-folder 16/74)
    - Patterson, Patrick J. (Box-folder 16/75)
    - Patton, Gwendolyn M. (Box-folder 16/76)
    - Paul, Cyril L. (Box-folder 16/77)
    - Payne, Niravi B. (Box-folder 16/78)
    - Payne, Velencia (Box-folder 16/79)
    - Pearmain, Diantha (Box-folder 16/80)
    - Pearson, Glen T. (Box-folder 16/81)
    - Pearson, Richard L. (Box-folder 16/82)
    - Pearson, Rosalee (Box-folder 16/83)
    - Peery, Lee (Box-folder 16/84)
    - Pellegrini, Mary Stewart (Box-folder 17/1)
    - Pendelton, James (Box-folder 17/2)
    - Pendleton, Robert E. (Box-folder 17/3)
    - Penman, Dorothy J. Grant (Box-folder 17/4)
    - Pennick, Aurie A. (Box-folder 17/5)
    - Peppers, Jason (Box-folder 17/6)
    - Perdew, John (Box-folder 17/7)
    - Perks, Bob (Box-folder 17/8)
    - Perry, Bernice L. (Box-folder 17/9)
    - Perry, Mary Ethel Williams (Box-folder 17/10)
    - Perry, William A., Jr. (Box-folder 17/11)
    - Peterson, Sheridan (Box-folder 17/12)
    - Petrea, Raymond A. (Box-folder 17/13)
    - Pettiford, Joseph B. (Box-folder 17/14)
    - Petty, Emma McCoy (Box-folder 17/15)
    - Pflager, Norma (Box-folder 17/16)
    - Phaup, Nancy (Box-folder 17/17)
    - Phillips, Geraldine (Box-folder 17/18)
    - Phillips, Loraine (Box-folder 17/19)
    - Phillips, Victoria (Box-folder 17/20)
    - Pierre, Vanilla (Box-folder 17/21)
      Includes photocopy of photographs.
    - Pierson, Lloyd M. (Box-folder 17/22)
    - Pilling, Patricia L. (Box-folder 17/23)
    - Pinkard, Linda T. (Box-folder 17/24/)
    - Pinkey, Walter (Box-folder 17/25)
    - Pippen-Johnson, Debra A. (Box-folder 17/26)
    - Pitts, Kathleen (Box-folder 17/27)
    - Player, Imogene L. (Box-folder 17/28)
    - Plowe, Ron (Box-folder 17/29)
    - Poe, Monika H. (Box-folder 17/30)
    - Poindexter, Lorraine (Box-folder 17/31)
    - Pollen, Ernestine (Box-folder 17/32)
    - Polsky, Dorthea (Box-folder 17/33)
    - Pons, Carolyn V. (Box-folder 17/34)
    - Poor, Linda (Box-folder 17/35)
    - Porfido, Frank M. (Box-folder 17/36)
    - Porter, Jim S. (Box-folder 17/37)
    - Potochnik, June (Box-folder 17/38)
    - Poulston, William (Box-folder 17/39)
    - Powe, Katrina (Box-folder 17/40)
    - Powell, Edward Phillip (Box-folder 17/41)
    - Powell, Shelley (Box-folder 17/42)
    - Prescott, Leopold "Ray" (Box-folder 17/43)
    - Proehl, Sharon D. (Box-folder 17/44)
    - Pryor, Martha H. (Box-folder 17/45)
    - Puckett, Donna (Box-folder 17/46)
    - Puffer, Phyllis (Box-folder 17/47)
    - Pullen-Smith, Barbara (Box-folder 17/48)
    - Purcell, Annie (Box-folder 17/49)
    - Purks, James H., III (Box-folder 17/50)
    - Purnell, Kathi (Box-folder 17/51)
    - Quatrone, Anthony R. (Box-folder 17/52)
    - Quillian, William F. (Box-folder 17/53)
    - T. R. (Box-folder 17/54)
    - Rabourn, James R. (Box-folder 17/55)
    - Race, Donald C. (Box-folder 17/56)
    - Rackley, Lurma (Box-folder 17/57)
    - Radosevich, Joseph J. (Box-folder 17/58)
    - Rafidi, Tommie Green (Box-folder 17/59)
    - Raftery, Marshall G. (Box-folder 17/60)
    - Ragin, Andrew L. (Box-folder 17/61)
    - Ragin-Williams, Sarah E. (Box-folder 17/62)
    - Ramirez, Sheri (Box-folder 17/63)
    - Ramsey, William R. (Box-folder 17/64)
    - Ransom, Elbert, Jr. (Box-folder 17/65)
    - Rasmussen, Donald E. (Box-folder 17/66)
      Includes essay with photographs.
    - Reardon, Carol L. (Box-folder 17/67)
    - Reed, Janice (Box-folder 17/68)
    - Reed, Tom (Box-folder 17/69)
    - Reed, Willis V., Sr. (Box-folder 17/70)
      Includes newsletter.
    - Reese, Greta (Box-folder 17/71)
    - Regan, Ronald C. (Box-folder 17/72)
    - Register, John (Box-folder 17/73)
    - Reid, Armstead (Box-folder 17/74)
    - Reiner, Barbara (Box-folder 17/75)
    - Reisman, Barbara J. (Box-folder 17/76)
    - Rennick, Everett (Box-folder 17/77)
    - Renz, Marion (Box-folder 17/78)
    - Repps, Ronald (Box-folder 17/79)
    - Reyes, F. B. "Lico" (Box-folder 17/80)
    - Rhames, Harold (Box-folder 18/1)
    - Rhodes, Annie P. (Box-folder 18/2)
    - Rice, Andrew (Box-folder 18/3)
    - Rice, Reginald (Box-folder 18/4)
    - Rich, Meredith (Box-folder 18/5)
    - Rich, William L. (Box-folder 18/6)
    - Richardson, Lorene (Box-folder 18/7)
      Includes program with news clippings and photographs.
    - Riggs, Helen (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Riley, C. J. (Box-folder 18/9)
    - Ripmaster, Terence M. (Box-folder 18/10)
    - Riss, Kathryn J. (Box-folder 18/11)
    - Rivas, Roman V. (Box-folder 18/12)
    - Roberts, Joe (Box-folder 18/13)
    - Roberts, Ken (Box-folder 18/14)
    - Roberts, Myrtice (Box-folder 18/15)
    - Roberts, Spurgeon A. (Box-folder 18/16)
    - Roberts-Joseph, Sadie (Box-folder 18/17)
    - Robertson, C. Alton (Box-folder 18/18)
    - Robischon, Thomas G. (Box-folder 18/19)
    - Robinson, Athan (Box-folder 18/20)
    - Robinson, Audrey Gray (Box-folder 18/21)
    - Robinson, C. B. (Box-folder 18/22)
    - Robinson, James E., Jr. (Box-folder 18/23)
    - Robinson, June (Box-folder 18/24)
    - Robinson, Leon R. (Box-folder 18/25)
    - Robinson, Lonnie Gregory (Box-folder 18/26)
    - Robinson, Lucious (Box-folder 18/27)
    - Robinson, Priscilla McLeod (Box-folder 18/28)
    - Robinson, Willie Louis (Box-folder 18/29)
    - Roby, Camille (Box-folder 18/30)
    - Rockafellow, Barbara (Box-folder 18/31)
    - Roddey, Cynthia (Box-folder 18/32)
    - Rodger, Phyllis (Box-folder 18/33)
    - Rodriguez, Ray (Box-folder 18/34)
    - Roe, Roger (Box-folder 18/35)
    - Roemer, Patricia (Box-folder 18/36)
    - Rodgers, Frankie (Box-folder 18/37)
    - Roman, Sergio (Box-folder 18/38)
    - Ronthaler, Edward (Box-folder 18/39)
    - Rooks, Nancy B. (Box-folder 18/40)
    - Rose, Kenneth A. (Box-folder 18/41)
    - Rosen, Rebecca (Box-folder 18/42)
    - Rosenblatt, Millie (Box-folder 18/43)
    - Rosen-Rieser, Phyllis (Box-folder 18/44)
    - Ross, Barbara C. (Box-folder 18/45)
    - Ross, Dina (Box-folder 18/46)
    - Ross, Ernest T. (Box-folder 18/47)
    - Ross, Lettie M. (Box-folder 18/48)
    - Roth, David (Box-folder 18/49)
    - Roth, Orville Francis (Box-folder 18/50)
    - Rothbart, Andrea (Box-folder 18/51)
    - Rowe, Bernice M. (Box-folder 18/52)
    - Rowe, Lackey (Box-folder 18/53)
    - Rowles, Billy E. (Box-folder 18/54)
    - Roy, Ralph Lord (Box-folder 18/55)
    - Ruben, Karl H. (Box-folder 18/56)
    - Ruder, Claire (Box-folder 18/57)
    - Rule, Robert A. (Box-folder 18/58)
    - Rushing, Robin (Box-folder 18/59)
    - Russell, James Charles (Box-folder 18/60)
    - Russell, Janet (Box-folder 18/61)
    - Rutledge, Rosa (Box-folder 18/62)
    - Rutledge, Steve (Box-folder 18/63)
    - Ryan, Charlton (Box-folder 18/64)
    - Ryan, I. (Box-folder 18/65)
    - Ryan, Jean (Box-folder 18/66)
    - Sackman, Carol (Box-folder 18/67)
    - Sadler, Wanda Pomeroy (Box-folder 18/68)
    - Saif, Anjum (Box-folder 18/69)
    - Salazar, Linda D. (Box-folder 18/70)
    - Saltzman, Murray (Box-folder 18/71)
    - Samperisi, John (Box-folder 18/72)
    - Sams, Fannie Baldwin (Box-folder 18/73)
    - Sand, Mary (Box-folder 18/74)
    - Sanders, Bernice G. (Box-folder 18/75)
    - Sanders, Richard R. (Box-folder 18/76)
    - Sandlin, Joan (Box-folder 18/77)
    - Sandoval, Delia (Box-folder 18/78)
    - Sands, Dorothylou (Box-folder 18/79)
    - Schillereff, Ruth Porter (Box-folder 18/80)
    - Schmidt, Helene (Box-folder 18/81)
    - Schneider, Richard H. (Box-folder 18/82)
    - Schoolfield, Zerlene (Box-folder 18/83)
    - Schrems, Jack (Box-folder 18/84)
    - Schwartz, Arthur A. (Box-folder 18/85)
    - Scoggins-Tenpenny, Evelyn Idell (Box-folder 18/86)
    - Scokk, Eunice (Box-folder 18/87)
    - Scott, John Weldon (Box-folder 18/88)
    - Scott, Mable Springfield (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Scott, Mary L. (Box-folder 19/2)
    - Scott, Walter R. (Box-folder 19/3)
    - Scruggs, Booker T., II (Box-folder 19/4)
    - Seaton, William (Box-folder 19/5)
    - Seay, Norman R. (Box-folder 19/6)
    - Seki, Don (Box-folder 19/7)
    - Senatore, Louise (Box-folder 19/8)
    - Sevlie, Patricia M. (Box-folder 19/9)
    - Seward, Betty (Box-folder 19/10)
    - Shabazz, Bilal (Box-folder 19/11)
    - Shaddeau, Sue (Box-folder 19/12)
    - Shah, Sunny (Box-folder 19/13)
    - Shamsud-Din, Lurlene Nafizah (Box-folder 19/14)
    - Shanks, Tom (Box-folder 19/15)
    - Shapiro, Dean M. (Box-folder 19/16)
    - Sharpe, Emanuel M. (Box-folder 19/17)
    - Sharpless, Gretchen (Box-folder 19/18)
    - Shaw, Lisa (Box-folder 19/19)
    - Shaw, Melvin P. (Box-folder 19/20)